module.exports = [
  {
    question:
      'Whats the name of the main character that said: "A Census Taker Once Tried To Test Me. I Ate His Liver With Some Fava Beans And A Nice Chianti."?',
    correctAnswer: "Dr. Hannibal Lecter",
    wrongAnswers: ["Norman Bates", "Jack Torrance", "Leatherface"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the villain in the movie "The Silence of the Lambs"?',
    correctAnswer: "Buffalo Bill",
    wrongAnswers: ["Norman Bates", "Hannibal Lecter", "The Zodiac Killer"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie involves a group of strangers trapped in a motel during a storm?",
    correctAnswer: "The Mist (2007)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Identity (2003)",
      "Saw (2004)",
      "The Texas Chainsaw Massacre (1974)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "Se7en"?',
    correctAnswer: "David Fincher",
    wrongAnswers: ["Martin Scorsese", "Quentin Tarantino", "Ridley Scott"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features a serial killer who uses the seven deadly sins as inspiration for his murders?",
    correctAnswer: "Se7en (1995)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Silence of the Lambs (1991)",
      "Memento (2000)",
      "The Usual Suspects (1995)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The Departed", which character is an undercover cop?',
    correctAnswer: "Billy Costigan",
    wrongAnswers: ["Frank Costello", "Colin Sullivan", "Queenan"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who played the role of the killer in the movie "Psycho"?',
    correctAnswer: "Anthony Perkins",
    wrongAnswers: ["Jack Nicholson", "James Stewart", "Martin Balsam"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the character played by Kevin Spacey in the movie "The Usual Suspects"?',
    correctAnswer: "Verbal Kint",
    wrongAnswers: ["Dean Keaton", 'Roger "Verbal" Kent', "Michael McManus"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features a character named Jigsaw who creates elaborate traps for his victims?",
    correctAnswer: "Saw (2004)",
    wrongAnswers: ["Scream (1996)", "The Purge (2013)", "Halloween (1978)"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "The Shining"?',
    correctAnswer: "Stanley Kubrick",
    wrongAnswers: ["Alfred Hitchcock", "Roman Polanski", "Steven Spielberg"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the character played by Clarice Starling in the movie "The Silence of the Lambs"?',
    correctAnswer: "Clarice Starling",
    wrongAnswers: ["Clarice Bill", "Clarice Barker", "Clarice Hamilton"],
  },

  {
    question:
      'In the movie "Seven", what is the sin associated with the victim whose head is found in a box?',
    correctAnswer: "Wrath",
    wrongAnswers: ["Greed", "Envy", "Lust"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The Departed", which actor played the undercover cop Billy Costigan?',
    correctAnswer: "Leonardo DiCaprio",
    wrongAnswers: ["Matt Damon", "Mark Wahlberg", "Jack Nicholson"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these movies was directed by Alfred Hitchcock?",
    correctAnswer: '"Vertigo" (1958)',
    wrongAnswers: [
      '"The Silence of the Lambs" (1991)',
      '"The Sixth Sense" (1999)',
      '"Memento" (2000)',
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these actors did NOT appear in the movie "Heat"?',
    correctAnswer: "Kevin Spacey",
    wrongAnswers: ["Al Pacino", "Robert De Niro", "Val Kilmer"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the character played by Jodie Foster in the movie "Panic Room"?',
    correctAnswer: "Meg Altman",
    wrongAnswers: ["Sarah Altman", "Emily Altman", "Jane Altman"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these movies was directed by David Fincher?",
    correctAnswer: '"Gone Girl" (2014)',
    wrongAnswers: [
      '"The Departed" (2006)',
      '"The Usual Suspects" (1995)',
      '"Se7en" (1995)',
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who played the lead role in the movie "Memento"?',
    correctAnswer: "Guy Pearce",
    wrongAnswers: ["Christian Bale", "Tom Hardy", "Edward Norton"],
  },
  {
    question:
      '"I see dead people." Which movie does this famous line come from?',
    correctAnswer: "The Sixth Sense (1999)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Silence of the Lambs (1991)",
      "Psycho (1960)",
      "Se7en (1995)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      '"You\'re gonna need a bigger boat." Which movie has this classic line?',
    correctAnswer: "Jaws (1975)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Psycho (1960)",
      "The Silence of the Lambs (1991)",
      "The Shining (1980)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who played the role of the Joker in the movie "The Dark Knight"?',
    correctAnswer: "Heath Ledger",
    wrongAnswers: ["Joaquin Phoenix", "Jared Leto", "Jack Nicholson"],
  },
];
